<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pactus 区块链</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/zh/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Pactus 区块链</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>zh</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/zh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh/contributing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh/contributing/</guid>
      <description>As an open-source platform, Pactus blockchain empowers from its community. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a developer, designer, or enthusiast, your contributions can make a meaningful impact.&#xA;There are several ways to support the Pactus project:&#xA;Run a Node One of the most effective ways to contribute to the Pactus network is by running a node. A &amp;ldquo;node&amp;rdquo; is a software program that downloads a copy of the Pactus blockchain and ensure the network keeps running safe and decentralized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh/user-guides/enable-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh/user-guides/enable-metrics/</guid>
      <description>Preface Pactus can be run with metrics, providing you with the ability to monitor your node. This tutorial will guide you through the steps to run Pactus with metrics, suitable for advanced users.&#xA;Prerequisites Before proceeding with the steps below, ensure that you have the following:&#xA;An understanding of Prometheus and Grafana. Have a running Pactus Node. Configure Pactus Node for Metrics To Configure the Pactus Node for Metrics, navigate to the Pactus directory; by default, it’s located at the following path.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh/user-guides/grpc-basic-auth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh/user-guides/grpc-basic-auth/</guid>
      <description>Preface The Pactus Blockchain offers a gRPC interface, enabling users to interact with both the blockchain and its native wallet. To enhance the security of gRPC APIs, we have implemented a Basic Authentication mechanism. This approach aims to provide a straightforward yet effective means for authenticating clients accessing the APIs.&#xA;Note: This mechanism secures gRPC, gRPC gateway, and HTTP communications.&#xA;Generate Basic Auth To enable basic authentication, you need to generate basic authentication credentials using an online tool or a predefined utility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh/user-guides/grpc-sign-transactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh/user-guides/grpc-sign-transactions/</guid>
      <description>Preface The Pactus Blockchain provides a gRPC interface that allows users to interact with the blockchain and native wallet. This is ideal for merchants and users who want to create, sign, and broadcast transactions using their local node. This tutorial will guide you step-by-step on how to use gRPC to sign transactions.&#xA;Setup node Initialize the node To follow along with this tutorial, you&amp;rsquo;ll first need to set up and run a localnet blockchain, which is suitable for testing:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh/user-guides/pactus-daemon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh/user-guides/pactus-daemon/</guid>
      <description>Preface Pactus can be run in different modes, including the command-line interface (CLI) and the graphical user interface (GUI). This tutorial will guide you through the steps to run Pactus in CLI mode, suitable for advanced users.&#xA;Prerequisites Before proceeding with the steps below, ensure that you have the following:&#xA;A computer running Windows, macOS, or Linux Suitable internet connection Download To get started, download and extract the Pactus CLI file from [here]({{ site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh/user-guides/pactus-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh/user-guides/pactus-docker/</guid>
      <description>Preface Docker is a tool that simplifies the process of creating, deploying, and running applications using containers. With containers, developers can bundle all the necessary parts of an application, including libraries and dependencies, and deploy them as a single package.&#xA;In this document, we will guide you on how to run Pactus using Docker, step by step.&#xA;Prerequisites The only thing you need is installing docker in your machine. If you are using Windows please make sure you have installed WSL.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh/user-guides/pactus-gui/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh/user-guides/pactus-gui/</guid>
      <description>序言 Pactus 可以在不同的模式下运行，包括命令行界面 (CLI) 和图形用户界面 (GUI)。 本教程将指导您完成在 GUI 模式下运行 Pactus，适合初学者到高级用户。&#xA;符合条件 在继续执行以下步骤之前，请确保您具备以下条件：&#xA;运行 Windows、macOS 或 Linux 的计算机。 互联网连接。 下载 从以下链接下载 Pactus GUI 安装程序。 [下链]({{ site.baseurl }}/download/#gui).&#xA;代码证书警告 Windows 和 macOS 用户可能会遇到一条警告消息，指出 Pactus 是不受信任的应用程序。 这是因为 Pactus 没有代码签名证书。&#xA;![Code certificate issue]({{ site.url }}/user-guides/pactus-gui/code-certificate-warning.png)&#xA;代码证书是验证软件发行者的身份和真实性的数字签名。然而，获得代码证书的过程复杂且昂贵，需要注册公司并 通过认识你的客户(KYC)检查。&#xA;由于 Pactus 是一个开源且基于社区的应用程序，所以我们还没有代码证书。 因此，您可以安全地忽略警告消息并继续安装 Pactus。&#xA;安装 要安装 Pactus GUI，只需按照安装程序提供的说明步骤进行操作即可。该过程非常简单，与在计算机上安装任何其他应用程序类似。&#xA;![Installing Pactus]({{ site.url }}/user-guides/pactus-gui/installing.png)&#xA;初始化 当您第一次运行 Pactus 时，将出现一个向导界面，指导您完成钱包创建和初始化过程。这个过程由几个步骤组成：&#xA;初始化模式 在第一页上，您会被询问您要如何创建钱包。选择“开始创建新钱包” 选项，然后进入下一页。&#xA;![Initialize mode]({{ site.url }}/user-guides/pactus-gui/initialize-mode.png)&#xA;钱包助记词 下一页将显示您的钱包助记词，由 12 个单词组成。安全备份此助记词至关重要，因为钱包恢复需要它以防您的计算机丢失、损坏或被盗。</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh/user-guides/pactus-wallet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh/user-guides/pactus-wallet/</guid>
      <description>Preface The Pactus Blockchain provides a wallet application that allows users to interact with the Pactus blockchain without the need to run a node. This is ideal for users who do not wish to operate a node but still want to create a personal wallet to manage their funds. This tutorial will guide you step-by-step on how to use the wallet application.&#xA;Download To get started, download and extract the Pactus CLI file from [here]({{ site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh/user-guides/reduce-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh/user-guides/reduce-network/</guid>
      <description>Preface Pactus is designed for low traffic usage. However, some users still face bandwidth limitations imposed by their Internet Service Providers (ISPs). This guide will explore effective ways to reduce networking usage for a Pactus node.&#xA;Reducing the number of connection By default, Pactus attempts to maintain 64 open connections with other nodes, split into 32 inbound and 32 outbound connections. To reduce networking usage, you can decrease this maximum number of connections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh/user-guides/send-transactions-gui/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh/user-guides/send-transactions-gui/</guid>
      <description>序言 Pactus 区块链提供了一个图形用户界面 (GUI), 带有内置钱包来创建, 签署并广播交易。 本教程旨在逐步指导您如何使用 GUI 应用程序将交易发送到 Pactus 区块链。 无论您是初学者还是高级用户, 本教程都适合您。&#xA;符合条件 在开始之前, 您需要运行 Pactus GUI 应用程序并确保它与网络同步。 您可以在此[教程]({{ site.baseurl }}/user-guides/pactus-gui/)中学习如何运行 Pactus GUI。&#xA;发送转账交易 如要发送[转账交易]({{ site.baseurl }}/learn/transaction/transfer/), 点击“交易”菜单并选择“转账”。 这将打开一个新窗口, 您可以在其中选择您希望发送转账的 [账户]({{ site.baseurl }}/learn/blockchain/account/)地址, 以及收款人的帐户地址和您希望发送的金额。&#xA;审核交易详情并确保其正确后, 单击“发送”按钮签署交易并将其广播到 Pactus 区块链。&#xA;![Transfer Transaction Dialog]({{ site.url }}/user-guides/send-transactions-gui/transfer-transaction-dialog.png)&#xA;需要注意的是, [交易费用]({{ site.baseurl }}/learn/transaction/fee/)将根据您发送的金额进行计算。&#xA;发送契约交易 如要发送[契约交易]({{ site.baseurl }}/learn/transaction/bond/), 点击“交易”菜单并选择“契约”。&#xA;点击后将出现一个新窗口, 您可以在其中选择您希望发送转账的账户地址, 以及[验证器]({{ site.baseurl }}/learn/blockchain/validator/)地址和您希望发送的质押金额。&#xA;如果验证器地址尚未在 Pactus 区块链上注册，您将需要提供验证器的公钥作为第一笔质押交易。这将在 Pactus 区块链上创建及验证您的验证器。 要获取公钥, 您可以钱包中右键单击验证者地址并选择“详细信息”。&#xA;![Bond Transaction Dialog]({{ site.url }}/user-guides/send-transactions-gui/bond-transaction-dialog.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
