<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>بلوكشين بكتوس&#34;</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/ar/</link>
    <description>Recent content on بلوكشين بكتوس&#34;</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>ar</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/ar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ar/contributing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ar/contributing/</guid>
      <description>As an open-source platform, Pactus blockchain empowers from its community. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a developer, designer, or enthusiast, your contributions can make a meaningful impact.&#xA;There are several ways to support the Pactus project:&#xA;Run a Node One of the most effective ways to contribute to the Pactus network is by running a node. A &amp;ldquo;node&amp;rdquo; is a software program that downloads a copy of the Pactus blockchain and ensure the network keeps running safe and decentralized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ar/user-guides/enable-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ar/user-guides/enable-metrics/</guid>
      <description>Preface Pactus can be run with metrics, providing you with the ability to monitor your node. This tutorial will guide you through the steps to run Pactus with metrics, suitable for advanced users.&#xA;Prerequisites Before proceeding with the steps below, ensure that you have the following:&#xA;An understanding of Prometheus and Grafana. Have a running Pactus Node. Configure Pactus Node for Metrics To Configure the Pactus Node for Metrics, navigate to the Pactus directory; by default, it’s located at the following path.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ar/user-guides/grpc-basic-auth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ar/user-guides/grpc-basic-auth/</guid>
      <description>Preface The Pactus Blockchain offers a gRPC interface, enabling users to interact with both the blockchain and its native wallet. To enhance the security of gRPC APIs, we have implemented a Basic Authentication mechanism. This approach aims to provide a straightforward yet effective means for authenticating clients accessing the APIs.&#xA;Note: This mechanism secures gRPC, gRPC gateway, and HTTP communications.&#xA;Generate Basic Auth To enable basic authentication, you need to generate basic authentication credentials using an online tool or a predefined utility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ar/user-guides/grpc-sign-transactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ar/user-guides/grpc-sign-transactions/</guid>
      <description>Preface The Pactus Blockchain provides a gRPC interface that allows users to interact with the blockchain and native wallet. This is ideal for merchants and users who want to create, sign, and broadcast transactions using their local node. This tutorial will guide you step-by-step on how to use gRPC to sign transactions.&#xA;Setup node Initialize the node To follow along with this tutorial, you&amp;rsquo;ll first need to set up and run a localnet blockchain, which is suitable for testing:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ar/user-guides/pactus-daemon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ar/user-guides/pactus-daemon/</guid>
      <description>Preface Pactus can be run in different modes, including the command-line interface (CLI) and the graphical user interface (GUI). This tutorial will guide you through the steps to run Pactus in CLI mode, suitable for advanced users.&#xA;Prerequisites Before proceeding with the steps below, ensure that you have the following:&#xA;A computer running Windows, macOS, or Linux Suitable internet connection Download To get started, download and extract the Pactus CLI file from [here]({{ site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ar/user-guides/pactus-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ar/user-guides/pactus-docker/</guid>
      <description>Preface Docker is a tool that simplifies the process of creating, deploying, and running applications using containers. With containers, developers can bundle all the necessary parts of an application, including libraries and dependencies, and deploy them as a single package.&#xA;In this document, we will guide you on how to run Pactus using Docker, step by step.&#xA;Prerequisites The only thing you need is installing docker in your machine. If you are using Windows please make sure you have installed WSL.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ar/user-guides/pactus-gui/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ar/user-guides/pactus-gui/</guid>
      <description>Preface Pactus can be run in different modes, including the command-line interface (CLI) and the graphical user interface (GUI). This tutorial will guide you through the steps to run Pactus in GUI mode, suitable for beginner to advanced users.&#xA;Prerequisites Before proceeding with the steps below, ensure that you have the following:&#xA;A computer running Windows, macOS, or Linux Suitable internet connection Download Download the Pactus GUI installer or archived file from [here]({{ site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ar/user-guides/pactus-wallet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ar/user-guides/pactus-wallet/</guid>
      <description>Preface The Pactus Blockchain provides a wallet application that allows users to interact with the Pactus blockchain without the need to run a node. This is ideal for users who do not wish to operate a node but still want to create a personal wallet to manage their funds. This tutorial will guide you step-by-step on how to use the wallet application.&#xA;Download To get started, download and extract the Pactus CLI file from [here]({{ site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ar/user-guides/reduce-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ar/user-guides/reduce-network/</guid>
      <description>Preface Pactus is designed for low traffic usage. However, some users still face bandwidth limitations imposed by their Internet Service Providers (ISPs). This guide will explore effective ways to reduce networking usage for a Pactus node.&#xA;Reducing the number of connection By default, Pactus attempts to maintain 64 open connections with other nodes, split into 32 inbound and 32 outbound connections. To reduce networking usage, you can decrease this maximum number of connections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ar/user-guides/send-transactions-gui/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ar/user-guides/send-transactions-gui/</guid>
      <description>Preface The Pactus Blockchain offers a Graphical User Interface (GUI) that comes with a built-in wallet to create, sign and broadcast transactions. This tutorial aims to guide you step-by-step on how to use the GUI application to send transactions to the Pactus blockchain. Whether you are a beginner or an advanced user, this tutorial is suitable for you.&#xA;Prerequisites Before we begin, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to run the Pactus GUI application and ensure that it is synced with the network.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
